omny.fm 2017-09-01

# Privacy Policy | Omny Studio

**About us**

This Privacy Policy explains what information 121cast Pty Ltd, 121cast, Inc and its related entities (together referred to as **Omny** ) collect about you and why, what we do with that information, how we share it, and how we handle the content you place in our products and services. It applies to all products, services and applications provided by Omny ( **Omny** **Services** ), including but not limited to those available on the websites specified below: 

  * omny.fm
  * omnystudio.com

By registering for or using Omny Services you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy. 

**Commitment to protecting privacy**

Privacy concerns are important to us. 

It is Omny’s policy to comply with the Australian Privacy Principles ( **Principles** ), as set out in the _Privacy Act 1988_ (Cth) ( **Privacy** **Act** ). 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and subject to, the Querys of Service applicable to the Omny Service you are using or accessing. Your use of Omny Services and any information you provide remain subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the applicable Omny Querys and Service. 

Where our services contain links to third-party websites, these sites are governed by their own privacy statements. Omny is not responsible for their operation, including but not limited to their information privacy practices. 

**Types of information collected**

When you use our services, we collect information about you, including personal information. Personal information is information that may be used to readily identify or contact you as an individual person, such as: your name, date of birth, gender, current and previous addresses, telephone or mobile numbers, email addresses, user names, and geographic information. 

We only collect personal information that is necessary for the function and activities of our business. For example, to access our paid or subscription services, we may require you to provide credit card or other payment information. We may also ask you to provide your username and password for third party websites or services in order to provide access to articles and information published on such sites. 

**Collection from third parties**

Where it is reasonable and practicable to do so, we will collect personal information about you only from you. We may sometimes be provided with information about you from a third party, such as a social networking site, or other site through which you have used our services. We will typically only do this with your consent. 

**Passive collection**

When you visit our website, our server attaches a small data file called a "cookie" to your computer’s memory. 

Cookies are pieces of information that may be transferred to your computer’s memory when you visit a website for record keeping purposes. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. However, if you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your web browser to refuse cookies. We use cookies to provide us with anonymous information on the use of our website and to know what you find interesting on our website. We do not link this information back to your identity or other information that you have provided to us. We do not store any information that identifies you inside cookies. 

In addition to the information that you provide to us when you use our services, we collect information about the URLs, titles and content of the web pages and other information you access through the Omny Services. The types of passive information we collect include your Internet Service Provider, IP address, browser type, device type, settings, time zone, language, and other information related to the manner in which you access the Omny Services. 

We also collect information about your use of the Omny Services, such as what you have read or viewed, which device you used to have access content, and what you choose to share with others. 

**Purpose of collection**

The primary purpose for collecting information is to enable Omny to better provide you with the Omny Services, in a manner tailored to your use of the services. We may also use the information collected for other secondary purposes related to this primary purpose. 

**Consequences of not providing information**

If you choose not to supply certain personal information, we may not be able to provide you with the level of service or the services you require. 

**General uses of information**

Some of the specific purposes for which we use the information we collect about you (including personal information to the extent applicable) include to: 

  * Provide, operate, maintain, improve, and promote Omny Services; 
  * Enable you to access and use Omny Services, including uploading, downloading, collaborating on and sharing content; 
  * Process and complete transactions, and send you related information, including purchase confirmations and invoices; 
  * Communicate with you, including responding to your comments, questions, and requests; providing customer service and support; providing you with information about services, features, surveys, newsletters, offers, promotions, contests and events; providing other news or information about us and our select partners; and sending you technical notices, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages; 
  * Monitor and analyse trends, usage, and activities in connection with Omny Services and for marketing or advertising purposes; 
  * Investigate and prevent fraudulent transactions, unauthorised access to Omny Services, and other illegal activities; 
  * Personalise Omny Services, including by providing content, features, or advertisements that match your interests and preferences; 
  * Enable you to communicate, collaborate, and share content with users you designate; and 
  * For other purposes about which we notify you. 

**Use of aggregated data**

We also may use the information we collect about you in an aggregate form. 

Aggregate data is information (originally personally identifiable or non-personally identifiable) that subsequently is used in aggregate form. 

Although aggregate data may be based in part on personally identifiable information about you, it does not identify you personally. We may use aggregate data we collect in order to conduct analysis or research, such as research about customer demographics, internet use, and interests and behaviour. We may share this type of aggregate data with a variety of third parties, including our affiliates, advertisers and other current and prospective business partners. As this form of data does not identify particular users, these third parties will not be able to contact you based solely on this data. 

Aggregate data may also be used for website administration, advertising, and promotional purposes, and we may share this information with various affiliated and unaffiliated entities. We may also enter into agreements with outside companies that possess the technology that allows us to customise the advertising and marketing messages you receive while using the Omny services. Your non-personally identifiable information and clickstream data about your activities may be shared with these companies so this customisation can be accomplished. Our agreement with these companies restricts them from sharing your information with third parties or using it for any other purpose. Clickstream and demographic information may also be shared with our advertisers and business partners. 

Omny may provide targeted advertisements based on information about you, such as your interests. Omny does not provide any personally identifiable information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad, although advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria. 

**Disclosure of information**

We may disclose your information to third parties who provide services to us, including organisations and contractors that assist us with the purposes for which we use your information. These services include: 

  * customer enquiries; 
  * installation, maintenance and repair services; 
  * operations, billing and debt-recovery functions; 
  * information technology and network services; 
  * market research and marketing services. 

We may also disclose your information: 

  * to your authorised representatives or advisors, or when you ask us to do so; 
  * to credit-reporting bodies and fraud-checking agencies, and to credit providers for credit related purposes such as credit-worthiness, credit rating, credit provision and financing; 
  * our related entities or our business partners; 
  * to organisations as required or authorised by law; 
  * to law enforcement and national security agencies, and other government and regulatory authorities as required or authorised by law; 
  * to third parties who assist us to manage or develop our business and corporate strategies and functions; 
  * for the purposes of facilitating or implementing a transfer/sale of all or part of our assets or business; 
  * to our contractors, consultants and service providers. 

**Protection and transmission of data**

Omny hosts data with hosting service providers in numerous countries including the **United States, Europe and Australia**. We may disclose your information to our hosting service providers or any other service providers in those countries or any other country in which we may conduct our business from time to time. 

We will ensure that all reasonable steps are taken to protect all personal information from misuse, interference, loss and unauthorised access, modification and disclosure. Although we seek to engage external service providers who also comply with these requirements, no security system is impenetrable and we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others. 

Accordingly, and to the extent permitted by law, we do not accept responsibility for the misuse of personal information while stored on our systems or otherwise in our care or in the care of our external service providers. 

**Third party analytics**

We have engaged Inspectlet to analyse the activities of visitors to this website, and Inspectlet's authorized use of cookies and other tracking technologies enable it to have access to Personal Information of visitors to this website. Such access to and use of Personal Information by Inspectlet is governed by [Inspectlet's privacy policy](https://www.inspectlet.com/legal#privacy). If you do not wish to participate in Inspectlet analytics, [opt-out of marketing site analytics](https://www.inspectlet.com/exclude/2032019773) and [opt-out of app site analytics](https://www.inspectlet.com/exclude/412716970). 

**Access to information**

You can access and amend some of the information we keep about you through your account settings. 

You also have a right to access your personal information otherwise held by us. We will take reasonable steps to correct any information you establish is not accurate, complete and up-to-date. To request access to any personal information we hold about you, contact us in writing via our contact details at the end of this Privacy Policy. All requests will be responded to within a reasonable period. To access any information we hold we will require you to verify your identity, and specify what information you require access to. 

We reserve the right to refuse access to your personal information if providing access would be unlawful or would have an unreasonable impact upon the privacy of other individuals. 

If you have subscribed to any of our newsletters or subscriptions, or are receiving promotional communications, and no longer wish to receive such communications, you may opt out of receiving them at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” button on any email communications that we send you or by contacting us at the details set out below. 

**Disposal of information**

We will take reasonable steps to destroy or de-identify personal information if it is no longer needed for any purpose for which it may be used or disclosed or if we are no longer required to retain the information at law. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make any changes, we will notify you by revising the ‘Last Updated’ date at the top of this Privacy Policy and, in some cases, where appropriate we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to the login screen or sending you an email notification). We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you use Omny Services to stay informed about our information practices and the ways you can help protect your privacy. 

If you disagree with any changes to this Privacy Policy, you must stop using Omny Services and deactivate your account(s). 

**Complaints about an interference with privacy**

If you consider that any action we take breaches this Privacy Policy or the Principles, you can make a complaint by contacting us at the address set out below. We will endeavour to act promptly in response to a complaint. 

**Contact**

For further information, or if you have any questions, comments, or concerns about any of the provisions of this Privacy Policy, please contact us: 

Attn: Compliance Officer  
121cast Pty Ltd   
62-66 King Street   
Melbourne, Victoria 3000   
AUSTRALIA 

Email: info@121cast.com
